Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical information of interviewees
    - Dalai Lama, 1987-1999 (Box 33, Folder 6-8)
      S880, 2636 and unspecified
    - Damon, Betsy, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - D'Amore, Louis J., 1971-2001 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
      2842
    - Danaher, Kevin, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      2919, 3037
    - Daniel, Alma, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dantes, Ligia, 1991-1999 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      2235
    - D'Antien, Mitani, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Darling, David, 1990-1998 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      2382
    - Darling, Diana, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Deep Ecology
      An innumbered program series
    - Darshan Singh, Sant, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dasmann, Raymond, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Deep Ecology is an unnumbered program series.
    - Dattatreya Siva Baba, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      3269
    - David, Bernard, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Davidson, Gordon, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Angela, 0000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Avram, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Daryl, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      3020
    - Davis, Roy Eugene, 1979-1984 (Box 35, Folder 14-15)
    - Davis, Rennie, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Dawkins, Peter, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Day, Laura, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      2612
    - De Domenico, Gisela, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Debold, Elizabeth, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      3104
    - Deida, David, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      mes is an unnumbered program series.
    - Deikman, Arthur MD, 1971-1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Delaney, Gayle, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      2553
    - Della, Madre Leslene, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      3137
    - Dellums, Ron, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Deloria, Vine Jr., 1999 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Demartini, John F., 2007 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      3192
    - Demby, Constance, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Deng, Ming Dao, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Dencker, Laurie and Charles Finkelstein, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Denver, John, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - DePalma, Bruce, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - DePorter, Bobbi, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - de Quincey, Christian, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      3136
    - Des Roches, Brian, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Detiger, Elinore, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Devall, Bill, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Unnumbered program series
      Deep ecology
    - Devall, Norman, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Dhiegh, Khigh Alx, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Dhiravamsa, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Diamond, Jed, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      3184
    - Diamond, John, 1979-1988 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Diaz, Adriana, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Di Benedetto, Romeo, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Dickinson, Dee, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Didion, Joan, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Dierks, Sheila Durkin, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Dierks, Sheila Durkin, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Dillard, Annie, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - DiPrima, Diane, 1992-1994 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Dirsmith, Ron and Suzanne Dirsmith, 1990-2000 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - diZerega, Gus, 1993-1998 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Unnumbered series
    - Dobson, Terry (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Dolan, Paul, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Program series
      Number 3031
    - Dominguez, Joe and Vicki Robin, 1981-1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Dowd, Michael and Connie Barlow, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        3152
      - Downing, Christine (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Drengson, Alan Rike, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Dozzer (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Drasin, Dan, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Dreher, Diane (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Dubosque, Doug and Susan Dubosque, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 14, 15)
      - Duce, Murshida Ivy O, 1981-2000 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Duff, Kat, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 17)
        2410
      - Dugan, Daniel, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Duggan, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Duggan, Robert, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Donald, Mary Ellen (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Donner, Florinda, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Dorris, Michael, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Dossey, Barbara, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Dossey, Larry M.D., 1982-2006 (Box 38, Folder 10-12)
      An unnumbered program series
    - Doty, Thomas, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Douglas, Barbara, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Dougals, Susan J., 2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Dowd, Michael, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      3252
    - Dowd, Michael and Connie Barlow, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Program number 3132
    - Downing, Christine (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Downing, John, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Dozzer (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Draper, Tom, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Dreher, Diane (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Drasin, Dan, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Drengson, Alan Rike, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Dubin, Judith see Melanie Keveles (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Dubosque, Doug and Susan Dubosque, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
    - Duce, Murshida Ivy O., 1981-2000 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Duff, Kat, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Dugan, Daniel, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Duggan, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Duhl, Leoanard, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Duke, James, 1986-1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Duncan, David James, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Dunning, Cliff, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Dwoskin, Hale, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      3209
    - Dwyer, Molly, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      3270
    - Dychtwald, Ken (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Dyer, Wayne, 1981-2000 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
      1774, 1987, 2153, 2349, 2622, 2814
    - Dyson, Elizabeth and Burton Dyson, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Dyson, Freeman, 1992-2000 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Dyveke, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Dzogchen, Ponlop, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      3208
    - Dzongsar, Khyentse, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Brooke Medicine Eagle, 1986-2000 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
      2105, 2308, 2844, 2846
    - Eswaran, Eknath, 1989-2005 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Eco, Umberto, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Edelen William, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Edwards, Betty, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Edwards, Corinne, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Edwards, Sharry, 1989-2003 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
      2509, 2332
    - Ehrenreich, Barbara, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Ehrlich, Paul and Anne Ehrlich, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Eisen, Saul, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      3116
    - Eisenberg, David, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Eisenber, Howard, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Eisler, Riane, 1987-2007 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
      2934, 3231
    - Eldridge, Lynne, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      3229
    - Elgin, Duane and Ann Niehaus, 1983-2000 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
      2652
    - Elkes, Joel, 1979-1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Ellis, Dave, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      3059
    - Ellsberg, Daniel and Patricia Ellsberg, 1981-2004 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Elmer, Lon, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Elstrott, Kelly, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Emery, George and Joelle Emery, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Emoto, Dr. Masaru, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Engler, Jack (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - English, Jane, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Ensler, Eve, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      3029
    - Epstein, Mark, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      2785
    - Erhard, Werner, 1977-1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      1480
    - Eritrea, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Estes, Clarissa Pinkloa, 1992-1994 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Evenson, Dean, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Everett, Alexander, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Eversoul, Philip, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Fadiman, Dorothy, 1987-2002 (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
      2684, 2908
    - Faludi, Susan, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Farrakhan, Louis, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Farrow, Jim, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Faryal, Tahmeena, 2001-2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Fassel, Diane, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Fastwolf, Oh Shinnah, 1977-1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fath, Tom, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Feenstra, Mark, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      3236
    - Feinstein, David, 1987-1996 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Feld, Steven, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Feldenkrais, Moshe, 1977-2000 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Felt, Joan, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      3156
    - Ferguson, Gary, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Ferguson, Marilyn, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      1784
    - Ferguson, Tom, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      2590
    - Ferrris, Timothy, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Feueurstein Georg, 1988-1994 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Fields, Rick, 1991-1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      1645, 2295
    - Fields, Sally, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Findeisen, Barbara, 1995-2003 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      2533, 2661, 2871
    - Fine, Ada B., 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Fineberg, Jill/The Box, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Finley, Guy, 2003-2008 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      2976, 3065, 3275
    - F.I.R.E Women, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Firestone, Robert, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Firth Murray, Anne, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      3191
    - Fisher, MFK, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Fisichella, A., 1973-1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Fjell, Judy, 1994-2008 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      Program mnumber
      3250
    - Fleming, Peggy, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      2795
    - Fletcher, Colin, 1984-1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      2640 and unspecified
    - Flinders, Carol Lee, 1998-2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      3161
    - Florin, Fabrice, 1977-1979 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Folin, Lilas, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Ford, Arielle, 1999-2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Ford, Clyde, 1990-2000 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      2311, 2817
    - Ford, Debbie, 2001-2003 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      2685, 3000
    - Ford, Gordon Onslow, 1992-1997 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Ford-Gilbert, Alyce, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Ford-Grabowsky, Mary, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      2931
    - Foreman, Dave, 1990-1998 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      An nunnumbered program seires
    - Forsee, David, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      2775
    - Foster, Stephen and Meredith Foster, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fotter, Steve, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Frager, Robert, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      2684
    - Francine, Anthea, 1989-2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Franck, Frederick, 1993-1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      2544
    - Franklin, Wink, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Franquemont, Sharon, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Frantlis, Ruce K., 2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      Spirit of the times
    - Freher-Lyons, Donna, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Freitas, Jacqlyn, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Fretwell, Claire, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Freudberg, David, 1988-1999 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Friedman, Norman, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Friedman, Rahina, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Frischknech, Martin, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Frisk, Trudy, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Fritz, Robert, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Frock, Linda, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
      3070
    - Frock Roger, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
      3071
    - Fukuoka, Masanobu, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Fulghum, Robert, 1988-1993 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Fuller, Bob, 1982-2008 (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
      1291,1842, 2672, 2869, 2896, 2983, 3069, 3152, 3271
    - Fuller, Millard, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Funk, Robert W., 1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Gabriel, Peter, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Gadon, Elinor, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Gaines, Jack, 1964-1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Gallagher, Winifred, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Galland, China, 1990-1998 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      2255
    - Fuller, Buckminster, 1967-2003 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
      1606
    - Gandhi, Arun, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Gandhi, Ramchandra, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Gangaji, 1994-2007 (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
      2609, 3225
    - Garcia, Jerry, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Gardner, Barbara, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      2746
    - Garfield, Charles, 1983-2007 (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
      1879, 2514, 2686
    - Garfiled, Laeh Maggie, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      1979
    - Garfiled, Patricia, 1988-2001 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      An unnumbered program seires
    - Gass, Robert, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      2759
    - Gary, Tracy, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Gaskin, Stephen, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      2237
    - Gates, Bill, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Gates, Jeff, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      2761
    - Gatto, John Taylor, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Gavs, Andy, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Gawain, Chi-uk, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gawain Shakti, 1985-1997 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      2437, 2696
    - Gebre, Bogaletch, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      3019
    - Gelb, Michael, 2001-2008 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      3234
    - Geller, Uri (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Gellert, Michael, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      3240
    - Gendler, Ruth, 1985-2007 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      3232
    - Gendlin, Eugene, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      1594
    - George, Demetra, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - George, Jay, 1994-1997 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - George, Laura, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      3190
    - Georgiou, Steve T., 2003 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Gerken, Siegmar, 1993-1998 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Gerard, Glenna (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Gerbner, George, 1993-2000 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      2703
    - Gershon, David, 1993-2007 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      3224
    - Gerson, Mark, 1982-2007 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      2559 and unspecified
    - Gignoux, Jane Hughes, 2000-2003 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      2979
    - Gilbert, David, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Gilbert, Zen Master Don, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Gilkyson, Eliza, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Gilkyson, Eliza, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Gilette, Douglas, 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Gilliam, Harold, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Gilman Robert and Diane Gilman, 1989-1999 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Gimbutas, Marija, 1989-1994 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      2307 and unspecified
    - Gingrich, Newt, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1976-1997 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Ginsburg, Judge Ruth (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Giovanni, Nikki, 1990-1994 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Giuliando, Daniel, 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Gladstar, Rosemary, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Gladwell, Malcolm, 1998-2003 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Glaser, Sherry, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Glass, Martin, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Glasser, Harold, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Glassman, Bernard, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Glendinning, Chellis, 1986-2000 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      2107, 2500
    - Glickstein, Lee, 1994-2002 (Box 56, Folder 10-11)
      2754, 2961
    - Globus-Sabori, Julia, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Goenka, S. N., 1981-2002 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      2948
    - Goin, Peter, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Golas, Thaddeus, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Gold, E. J., 1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Gold, Ellis, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Gold, Peter (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Goldberg, Buryon, 1994-2000 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      2490
    - Goldberg, BZ, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Goldberg, Natalie, 1990-2004 (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
      2213, 2376, 2662, 3067
    - Goldberg, Philip (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Goldes, Mark, 1977-1987 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Goldhammer, John D., 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Goldman, Jonathan and Andi Goldman, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
      3176
    - Goldstein, Joseph, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Goleman, Daniel, 1993-2005 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      2411, 2548, 2743, 2864, 3120
    - Goleman, Tara Bennett, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      2864
    - Goodall, Jane, 1995-1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      2774
    - Goodkin, Doug, 1991-1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Goodman, Amy, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Gorbachev Foundation, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Gordon, David Cole, 1972-1975 (Box 58, Folder 7-8)
    - Gordon, Marilyn, 1991-1994 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Goswami, Amit, 1993-2001 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
      2409, 2561, 3272
    - Gottlieb, Freema, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      2225
    - Graeb, Jim, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Graham, Jerry, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Grandin, Temple, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      3075
    - Grant, David, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Grasso, Barbara, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Gray, John, 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Gray, Leslie, 1989-2002 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      2214, 2909
    - Gray, Spalding, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Grebenshikov, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Greco, Thomas H. Jr., 2002 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      Spirit of the Tmes
    - Green, Elmer, 1992-2004 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Green, Jerry, 1974-1980 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Green Michael, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Greenberg, Michael, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Greenfield, Larry, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Greer, Mary K., 1994 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Greene, Larry, 1976-1977 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Gregg, Susan, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      2887
    - Greider, William, 1997-2003 (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
      2608
    - Griffin, Susan, 2002-2003 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
      2936, 3013
    - Griffiths, Fr. Bede, 1983-2005 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      2273, 2495, 3009
    - Griscom, Chris, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Grof, Stanislav and Christina Grof, 1985-1998 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
      2446
    - Gross, Albert, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Grosscup, Beau, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Grossinger, Richard (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Grossman, Richard, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Grosso, Michael, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      2535
    - Grumbine, Ed, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Gumbleton, Bishop Thomas, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Gurian, Michael, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      2492
    - Gurumayi, Chidvilasananda, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Haas, Elson M., 2000-2006 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      2826, 3131
    - Hadley, Leila, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Haenke, David, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Hagelin, John, 1996-1999 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Haisch, Barnard, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      3159
    - Halifax, Joan, 1985-1997 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - Hallen, Patsy, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Halpern, Charles, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      3245
    - Halpern, Steve, 1988-2001 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Halpern, Susan P., 2004-2008 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      3244
    - Halprin, Anna, 1987-2002 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Halprin Sara, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      2528
    - Hamburg, Dan, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      2389
    - Hamilton, Craig, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      3107
    - Hamilton, Vijali, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
      2390
    - Hammerschlag, Carl, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Hammond, Debra, 2004-2005 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      3064, 3127
    - Handler, Maris, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      3217
    - Handy, Charles, 1990-1994 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Hannaford, Carla, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Hansen, Mark Victor, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      Program number 2995
    - Harak, Rev. Simon G., 2001-2002 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Harburg, Jennifer K., 1993-1997 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Harden, Lakota (Box 63, Folder 13)
      Cassette: Lakota Harden interviewed by Penny Rosenwasser, an unproduced original
    - Hardin, Jesse Wolf, 1994-2004 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
      3053
    - Hardin, Loba, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Harding, Doulgas, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Hare, Chauncey, 1996-1998 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Harman, Willis, 1987-1996 (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
      2446, 2558, 2083 and unspecified
    - Harner, Michael, 1990-2000 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Harney, Corbin, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      3006
    - Harp, David, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Harrington, John, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Alice, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Sam, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      2470
    - Harrison, Hugh, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Harrison, Lou, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Hart, Diana, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      3169
    - Hart, Gary, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Hart, Mickey, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 10-11)
      2210
    - Hartke, Jan (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Hartmann, Thom, 2000-2004 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      2807, 3061
    - Harvey, Andrew, 1991-2002 (Box 66, Folder 3-4)
      2451, 2646, 2647, 2648
    - Harvey, Bill (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Harvey Richard, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Hastings, Anne Stirling, 1994-1996 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Hatcher, Terri, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Hauck, Louise, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Havel, Vaclav, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Hawk, Cathy and Gary Hawk, 1988-2007 (Box 66, Folder 11-12)
      2753, 3090, 3226
    - Hawken, Paul, 1983-1999 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
      2757
    - Hawkes, Joyce Whitely, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      3183
    - Hawkins, David R., 2003 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Hawley, Dave and Kumar Plocher, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Hay, Louise, 1985-1987 (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
      2641
    - Hayden, Tom, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Young, Margaret Hayes, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      Anunnumbered program series
    - Heckler, Richard S., 1990 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Hedua, Beth, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      2657
    - Heerman, Barry, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      3036
    - Hegarty, Christopher, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Heinberg, Richard, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      3079
    - Heiniger-White, Margot, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      2661
    - Heinze, Ruth-Inge, 1991-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
      2213
    - Helminski, Kabir and Camille Helminski, 1993-1996 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Henderson, Hazel, 1973-1995 (Box 68, Folder 8-9)
      2231, 2804
    - Heller, David, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Hendricks, Gay, 1993-2005 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      2421, 2518, 3096
    - Henn, Jamie and May Boeve, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      3102
    - Herbert, Anne, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Hermach, Timothy, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Hershman, Sophia (Sandy), 2000 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Hertsgaard, Mark, 1999-2003 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      2772, 2971
    - Hewlett, Marty, 2001-2006 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      3054, 3171
    - Heyneman, Martha, 1993-1996 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Hickman, James, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Hiestand, Denie, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      Cassette tape: Radio interview with Denie Hiestand "Back to Life"
    - Higgins, Colin, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - High Bear, Martin, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      2363
    - Hightower, Jim, 1990-1993 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Hiley, Basil J., 1994-1997 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Hilgendorf, Brian, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Geoffrey, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Hill, Julia "Butterfly", 1998-2002 (Box 69, Folder 15-16)
      2805, 2815, 2942
    - Hill, Michael Ortiz, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      3265
    - Hillier, Gina Mazza, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Hillman, Anne (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Hillman, James, 1989-1997 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      2333
    - Hirsch, Carl (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Hirschann, Jane and Carol Munter, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Hirshfield, Jane, 1994-2006 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      2486, 3170
    - Hiss, Tony, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Hixon, Lex, 1989-1992 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Hock, Dee W., 1994-2001 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      2789, 2790
    - Hoffman, Albert, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Hoffman, Bob (Fischer-Hoffman), 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Hoffman, David, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      2850
    - Hoffman, David and Iris Hoffman, 1984-1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Hoffmann, Heidrun, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 3)